<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>churchintouraine.org</title>
    <link href="https://churchintouraine.org/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://churchintouraine.org" />
    <updated>2023-06-15T23:22:13+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Church of St Alcuin of York</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://churchintouraine.org</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Welcome to the Touraine and the church of St Alcuin of York </title>
        <author>
            <name>Church of St Alcuin of York</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://churchintouraine.org/welcome-to-the-touraine-and-the-church-of-st-alcuin-of-york/"/>
        <id>https://churchintouraine.org/welcome-to-the-touraine-and-the-church-of-st-alcuin-of-york/</id>

        <updated>2023-06-15T23:22:13+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    ST ALCUIN’S is a worshipping community of the Diocese in Europe, the Church of England, and the worldwide Anglican Communion. We offer a very warm welcome to all who want to celebrate the love of God with us and hope you enjoy our service. We&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>ST ALCUIN’S is a worshipping community of the Diocese in Europe,
the Church of England,
and the worldwide Anglican Communion.
We offer a very warm welcome to all who want to celebrate the love of God with us and
hope you enjoy our service.
We come together to celebrate the presence of Christ in word and sacrament: the Holy
Communion or Eucharist—
    <em><strong>the Lord’s own Service
    for the Lord’s own People
    on the Lord’s own Day.</strong></em></p>
<p>And so we follow Our Lord’s command *** “Do this in memory of me”***
as the Church has done ever since her earliest days (Acts 2.42; Acts 20.7).</p>
<p>We are part of the Church of England and our worship follows the Anglican pattern. But
we are not an exclusive group: we are pleased to welcome people of any Christian
background—or none. We aim to be a Church for every English-speaking Christian, a
spiritual home for all who want to worship in English.</p>
<p>As our name implies our home is the 2,366 square miles of the Indre-et-Loire département of France (Touraine is its traditional name), but we cover a much wider area than that. We draw regular worshippers from no fewer than three different regions.</p>
<p>So, whether you live here, or are visiting, we warmly invite you to join us.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
